<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog | Шарофиддинов Зийнатулло</title>
    <link>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/media/icon_hu_645fa481986063ef.png</url>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for the New Semester</title>
      <link>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-week-from-july-23-to-july-29&#34;&gt;📌 Week from July 23 to July 29&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vacation is reaching its midpoint, and I decided to do a bit of preparation for the upcoming semester. I made a list of subjects to be studied and found several online courses to deepen my knowledge in databases and analytics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also disassembled my laptop, cleaned the cooling system, and updated some software — now the equipment is ready for new workloads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Little by little, I can feel the anticipation of returning to the university atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Nature</title>
      <link>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-week-from-july-16-to-july-22&#34;&gt;📌 Week from July 16 to July 22&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week was spent outdoors — my friends and I went out of town. Tents, a campfire, evening conversations, and a starry sky — exactly what was needed after an intense academic year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the day, we swam in the lake and went boating, and in the evening, we experimented with a bit of campfire cooking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trips like this help to reset and return to tasks with renewed energy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Projects and Self-Development</title>
      <link>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-week-from-july-9-to-july-15&#34;&gt;📌 Week from July 9 to July 15&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week, I started working on a small project — a chatbot for automating simple tasks. I’m using Python and a library for message processing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, I’m reading a book on algorithms that I didn’t manage to fully cover during the semester. It’s fascinating to see how the theory studied at the university is now applied to real-world problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though the vacation is in full swing, I try to dedicate a couple of hours a day to studying and practice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Day of Vacation — Long-Awaited Rest</title>
      <link>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-week-from-july-2-to-july-8&#34;&gt;📌 Week from July 2 to July 8&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exam session has finally ended, and the long-awaited summer vacation has begun. The very first thing I did was simply sleep in without an alarm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I met up with friends in the park — we walked around and recalled the funniest moments of the past semester. The weather is perfect — it’s the best time for walks and trips out of town.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve planned a few small programming projects for July to stay in shape, but for now, I’m just enjoying my free time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session — Final Push Before the Holidays</title>
      <link>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ZiynatulloSharofiddinov.github.io/en/post/01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-week-from-june-25-to-july-1&#34;&gt;📌 Week from June 25 to July 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The week was spent in full concentration mode — the exam session was in full swing. The exams in economics and computer science turned out to be more challenging than expected: I had to dedicate a lot of time to reviewing lectures and solving past years’ problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The algorithms exam was especially memorable — one of the tasks involved code optimization, and the solution came literally a couple of minutes before the end. The adrenaline was off the charts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the fatigue, there’s a real sense of satisfaction from the work done. Only a couple more subjects left — and then I can finally relax.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
